followerwonk.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy

QuestRight LLC ("Company," "QuestRight," or "we") respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy.

QuestRight offers various services (the "Services") to provide businesses and individuals with social media analytics, known as Followerwonk. The Services include access to the website at [followerwonk.com](https://followerwonk.com/) and any related website or domain or application operated by Company (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the [Terms of Use](https://followerwonk.com/terms-of-use).

This privacy policy describes the types of information we may collect from you, from your use of our Site or Services, and from Twitter, Inc.; it also describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

## This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On the Site.

  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and the Site.

  * Through applications you download from the Site or in connection with the Services, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and the Site.

  * From publicly available information through Twitter.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.

This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to our Privacy Policy below). Please check the policy periodically for updates.

## Children Under the Age of 16

Our Site is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on the Site or on or through any of its features, register on the Site, make any purchases through the Site, use any interactive or public comment features of the Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at: [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com?subject=Under%20age).

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

**We collect several types of information from and about users of our Site and Services and Twitter users. The information we collect is summarized here and described in more detail below:**

  * your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, and Twitter display name and username ("contact information");

  * information about your employment, such as your company name and job title, or interests, or that is publicly available through Twitter ("bio information"); and/or

  * information about your Internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Site and about your usage of our Services ("usage information").

**We collect this information:**

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.

  * From your use of our Site or Services through cookies and other technologies.

  * From third parties, for example, our business partners and third-party service providers with whom you have authorized us to collect data (e.g. Twitter).

## Information You Provide to Us

**The information we collect on or through our Site or Services includes:**

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site. This includes without limitation information provided at the time of subscribing to the Services (e.g. Twitter access tokens, Twitter usernames), and when you report a problem with our Site.

  * Information about the devices you use with the Services, such as last login Internet Protocol (IP) address.

  * Credit card information, including credit card brand, the last four digits of your credit card number, and month and year of expiration.

  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.

  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.

  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Site and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Site.

  * Your search queries on the Site.

  * Information you enter into our Site about your marketing activities so that we can provide Services to you.

You also may provide information to be published, displayed or transmitted (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Site, or transmitted to other users of the Site or third parties. You choose to post publicly viewable content and transmit information to other users of the Site or third parties at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other users of the Site with whom you may choose to share your content. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee any limitations on the usage of content that you chose to share with the public, other users of the Site or third parties.

## Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies

**As you navigate through and interact with our Site and Services, we collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:**

  * Details of your visits to our Site, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Site.

  * Information about your computer and Internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

**The information we collect helps us** **with security, to improve our Site and Services, and to deliver better and more personalized future services by enabling us to do things such as:**

  * Provide information to assist in determining whether there has been unauthorized access of your account.

  * Keep the Site and Services available and functioning with rate limiting.

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Site according to your individual interests.

  * Speed up your searches.

  * Recognize you when you return to our Site.

  * Provide better services in the future.

**The technologies we use to collect data from your use of our Site and Services may include:**

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file stored on your computer. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site.

  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Site and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

## Information We Collect From Third Parties

**We collect information from publicly available Twitter accounts, including:**

  * Twitter User ID

  * Screen Name

  * Full Name

  * Account Creation Timestamp

  * Friends Count

  * Followers Count

  * Bio information

  * Tweets Count

  * Location

  * Language

  * Protected (true/false)

  * Verified (true/false)

  * URL

  * Profile Image URL

  * Follower IDs

  * Following IDs

## How We Use Your Information

**We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:**

  * To provide our Site and Services to visitors and users of our Site and Services.

  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.

  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.

  * To provide you with notices about your subscriptions to the Services, including expiration and renewal notices.

  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.

  * To notify you about changes to our Site or any products or services we offer or provide though it.

  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Site.

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We never sell your contact information or provide it to others for marketing purposes.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may collect and disclose anonymous and aggregated information about our users and subscribers, and other information that does not identify any individual, without restriction for the purposes of product research, to improve our Services, and for other commercial purposes.

**We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:**

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an email address to use an email feature, we will transmit the contents of that email and your e-mail address to the recipients.

  * To vendors working on our behalf as necessary to complete transactions or provide the Site and Services.

  * In connection with a sale of the company, or substantially all its assets or the applicable business division to which your account relates.

  * With your consent to our subsidiaries, affiliates, or other third parties.

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.

  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of QuestRight, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

**We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:**

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.**  You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of the Site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.**  You can subscribe to receive promotional offers from the Company about our products and services or third parties' products and services by checking the relevant box(es) located on the form in which you provide us with your contact information. If you no longer wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own products or services, you can opt-out at any time by logging into the Site and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com?subject=Opt-out). If we have sent you a promotional e-mail, you may use the unsubscribe link included in each promotional-mail or send us a return email asking to be omitted from future e-mail distributions. This opt-out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.

## Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Site and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an e-mail at [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com?subject=Privacy%20Issue) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. In some cases, we cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Content from the Site, copies of publicly viewable content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other users of the Site. Proper access and use of information provided on the Site, including User Content, is governed by our [Terms of Use](https://followerwonk.com/terms-of-use).

## EU Data Subject Rights

## LAWFUL GROUNDS

If you reside in the European Economic Area or Switzerland (collectively the "EU"), we rely on the following lawful grounds under the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR") to process (collect, store, and use) your personal data: (a) it is necessary for the performance of a contract; (b) our or a third party's legitimate business interest; or (c) your consent. Our Clients determine the lawful grounds for the processing of personal data submitted through their use of our Services and we limit such processing to our Clients' instructions.

## DATA TRANSFER NOTICE

We are located in the United States. We use model contractual clauses with our Clients to provide adequate protection for the transfer and processing of your personal data in the United States.

## INDIVIDUAL RIGHTS

You may contact us at [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com) to request access to, transfer of, and rectification or erasure of your personal data, or restriction of processing, or to object to processing of your personal data. Please specify the nature of your request and the information that is the subject of your request. We may require you to submit additional information necessary to verify your identity and status as an EU data subject. If we are processing your personal data for a client, we will forward your request to our client and assist the client in responding within 30 days. If you are a visitor or user of our Services, we will respond to your request directly within 30 days.

If we are processing your personal data based upon the lawful ground of your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent for such processing at any time without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before it is withdrawn. To withdraw consent, email us at [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com).

## RETENTION

At a minimum, we will retain your personal data for a long as necessary for the purpose in which it was collected such as to perform a contract, for our or a third party's legitimate interest, or your consent. Unless you request deletion of your personal data sooner, we may hold your personal data for 365 days.

## YOUR CHOICES; COOKIES

  * Submission of Personal Information. You may, of course, decline to submit information through the Services, but we may not be able to provide all or a portion of the Services to you.

  * Cookies. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies in the browser settings if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use certain Services and/or Third-Party Services features that depend on cookies.

**Contact Us**. If you receive commercial e-mail from us, you may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained within the e-mail. You may also opt-out from receiving commercial e-mail from us, and any other promotional communications that we may send to you from time to time by sending your request to us by e-mail at [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com) or by writing to us at: QuestRight, Attn: Privacy, PO Box 14065, Spokane Valley, WA 99214.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com) or write us at: QuestRight, PO Box 14065, Spokane Valley, WA 99214.

## Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Site like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Site.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site or via our Services.  **Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk.** We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site or via the Services.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the primary email address specified in your account and/or possibly through a notice on the Site home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Site and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at [help@followerwonk.com](mailto:help@followerwonk.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question).

Updated October 5, 2018.
